twittermail.com 2012-09-06

# TwitterCounter Privacy Policy

TwitterCounter Privacy Policy
TwitterCounter (“Service”), a service by The Next Web Holding BV (“TNW”), collects public data about
Twitter accounts, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information
on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey
information and/or site registrations). The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web
pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial
purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under
the following circumstances:
     •    It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal
          activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any
          person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
     •    We transfer information about you if TNW or TwitterCounter is acquired by or merged with
          another company. In this event, TNW will notify you before information about you is transferred
          and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
Information Gathering and Usage
     •    When you register for a paid TwitterCounter service we ask for information such as your name,
          company name, email address, billing address, credit card information.
     •    TNW uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services
          provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.
     •    Credit card information will never be stored by TNW, Twittercounter or on TNW servers, but by a
          third party payment provider.
Cookies
TwitterCounter uses cookies to collect data about usage of the Service and to improve the Service. A
cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your
computer's hard drive. TwitterCounter may use persistent cookies to improve user interaction with the
Service and to gather information on usage of any part of the Service, including but not limited to The
Visitor Widget.
The Visitor Widget
The Visitor Widget is a small piece of code that can be installed and used on third-party websites not
related to TwitterCounter. TwitterCounter uses cookies to collect and display data about users that visit
third-party websites with The Visitor Widget installed.

Data Storage
TNW uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software,
networking, storage, and related technology required to run TwitterCounter. TNW owns the code,
databases, and all rights to the TwitterCounter application.
Disclosure
TNW may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with
subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.
Changes
TNW may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat
personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your TwitterCounter
primary account holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
Questions
Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to sam@twittercounter.com or by mail at: The
Next Web Holding BV, Nieuwe Achtergracht 17, 1018 XV, Amsterdam, The Netherlands.
